I'm gonna need a dashboard cam because I
nearly had to stop at a red light and
here they recorded this at a red light I
realized that was not a tickle I had nor
say which makes an ethical um so yeah
the idea I think I had two ideas Oh a
hope let's see if I can um do I want you
to suffer videos the one that you've
denied you I had before there's some
ugly legality but being able to
communicate with other cars around you
not necessarily publicly but privately
so if I see someone's license plate and
it's for that province or state then
that's unique to them so I can say you
know thanks for letting me in
we need to be something heads boys
activated so people aren't texting and
driving or someone cuts you off someone
speeding you know you can do like props
and call-outs and yeah they're just a
lot of times that I would like to
communicate with drivers around me I
realize this will bring trollee into a
whole new level
but yeah that is Apple number 42